hi welcome back to the wheel of life
online retreat Xin chào German which are
like Watto took three months a new home
we've reached session number nine Subban
- zucchini and this is gonna be a
meditation my formation of a team and
some of you have done this meditation
before during the lion stance meditation
momentum socket by not on the convent
ignite chip I don't want a podium
shuttle but we're about to discuss the
Wheel of Life in detail a logitech
Levinson ooh hi
we've been talking about how to go from
one life to another life especially the
Bartok
I don't know very lumpy now daddy told
maki-chan keep it back Mitch and I to
come and now we're gonna explore that
well become fat dude ah by the way I
made a mistake and in the video
yesterday you came to dama Malloy jump
we don't um wha and I would like to
correct it
so there are two books about how to help
somebody in the puddle Oh shucks no man
I'm fine now now jump jack hi to mom and
the two names are very similar
young young and I made a mistake
yesterday so the first book is called
means just hearing about it you can be
liberated in the bottle
dig me a knock at my coat I don't get
out jumping high do mum and that's the
book which is not considered authentic
in in arts on carpet tradition
welcome to Shimla Denton Jeong ChiHong
kappa go Jota
you
and it has been translated in English as
the Tibetan Book of the Dead or names
like that get same thing unlike us at a
time like a chat what they tend to
neuter so I I would encourage you to
rather use the great ancient books on
the epidermis the title queen cadet
Mahoney say Yamaguchi Koshu of it I
don't be you fat that's the presentation
I made in this course what on a function
by toda to Kingdom Wahab 9 the book name
I used yesterday which is part of Chung
hong-won word difference google shuttles
a young man what about Tom Tom no Bob
that means freedom from the narrow
alleyway knocking Anna so talk a little
more hypo chant I too am
and that's a great book shut up together
so I made a mistake yesterday I
mentioned that book my dad a capital
Kinshasa and that that's a pretty famous
chunk choke or how to help somebody in
the burden padamu shot carnitine chancho
also yesterday or two days ago we
mentioned the word boom like in
miller-el past 100 songs I'm sorry I
don't wanna touch on where I'm opening a
chill to by the captain to public option
about cooking a meal average and the
usual name of his book is just like the
nickname is good boom boom boom shaka
minut and engli boom boom
so literally it means 100 thousand songs
done anything with a li mo Chou me and
Micah but the hundred thousand just
means a collection of his songs it's not
a hundred thousand ninja-ing kamila
opposite opinion by Kirk or may not come
phylum of Chong yang there's a similar
word Sylvan which means the collected
works of any modern Tibetan in the last
1000 years
come on Tonto goon show me an onion that
from show Tom Kubik king of the tanning
line out of a pairing number
so we I think we translated as 100 and
not 100,000 so it should be chance
there's 100,000 do better yet knock on
file I'm hangry
okay so we're gonna go through a
meditation which is part of the ancient
lion stands meditation which was taught
by Buddha and also Maitreya and a Sangha
do Kali do pass a big one Fontaine
gramophone cool thing Buddha shooter
goes to that I can get my phone in a
phone yet
Sangha and we're gonna go on a journey
to our past life Tomoko continued keep
to kakuta but the purpose of that is to
explore dependence or you can call it
which is the meaning of the twelve links
inside the wheel of life like oh my my
too much I'll go home we're gonna
be going deep into those traveling
starting with the next session session
10 so hungry me how much it topic now
the fun tip he'll phone someone and
there's a way that you can explore them
personally during the meditation my
Dibango take on 5 June tell that Canyon
don't shoot biting so let's do that
together we've I entertained you don't
kumbaya put on my meditation timer
dr. yang ba bum ya a note on this is a
nice timer I would use it it's called
inside timer
no Jesse yeah here we go get comfortable
and you're sitting on a tall mine a
little bit of a smile mentally I mean
course there are serious things
happening in the world
jump and say agenda yeah but it doesn't
mean we have to go around with a scowl
come on you notify ill and one wakening
coco to come bickner these are the kind
of times when people need a smile they
lining up on your comment okay
they need us to be friendly and warm
towards them well how can do that
taunting me huh
relax your forehead and how long Django
good man relax your fingers
I love me long time during the
meditation try not to tighten your
forehead or get wrinkles on your friend
so my technical game doesn't contain
hanging the first thing I find it very
useful to have a slight smile Canyon
todo taco what come on the eyes are
closed but they are focused a little bit
up I'm lying you know mocked up to man
pitch and move to and it's very good to
tighten the lower abdomen which
strengthens the back but I don't make a
twang ha boom you neither you shumlin
town so here we go
but now now we're gonna start this
meditation with 10 breath in topic now
I'm paying my way Muay Thai town
let's count 10 slow breaths if I have a
cowboy hat I'll jump jump by tradition
the out-breath the beginning of the
breath is the out-breath 15 tomato fight
ha ha hi tiger and remember that I'm
asking you at the end of your out-breath
to push out a little more when you're
done don't you conquer pain Wow go ahead
item to complete my
let's enjoy 10 long exhale press the
inhale will take care of itself
oh yeah yeah right about shadow Dom oh
look the king
you
and look to a quick seven seven step
preliminary which impartial opinion may
move my dog so please invite one of your
teachers to come and sit in front of you
if I belong my mob comes on you know how
you cook at my dive on your cheek my
dick man
you
now let's make them a gift yeah I found
your armoire of appreciation of some
great quality of theirs who shall come
get way more fight from Jackie boy Gua
think of something about your teacher
that you really admire he knew ye
doffing would I go back back mother
penny took sugar law
you
now let's clean some bird seeds from
yesterday yeah hey lunch at my why I'm
so - homework think of two or three
mistakes you made yesterday
I need a hi hey man no longer Panama
Friday my and open up your heart and
admit them to your teacher
Mahima long money but Jim Bowie no Tycho
get back make a promise not to repeat
them I not much account I found you for
some length of time double cuenta again
you
now give equal time and energy to
thinking about a few good things you did
yesterday and telling your teacher yeah
I anti-gang when I know you know then
why do you talk about alarm my about the
HIV tycoon man
you
no as for teachings in your life you
know you don't burn your welcome to
Gupta I get back some of them will come
as a positive teachings and some of them
will come as challenges oh boy um so
daughter done by young in my optical
form of items Oh does it have a young
intact
you
ask your teacher to please stay in your
life yeah a single tiny cocoa bang or
light emotion booked a crime
you can see a big difference between
people who have it close teacher and
people who don't
by the time option topic learn Union
don't come up with Titan take when
you'll come power one point I 20 April
lucky we have a teacher we can be
exhaustive I don't have my mom to come
up with hydrant a cation go
you
now let's go back to the beginning of
this preliminary steps yeah I way line
up now geun-young you tomorrow night we
are looking at the teacher in front of
us jingyan vomit I took my toolbar again
they are alive and they're warm they're
a real person on a Makita now try to
imagine something about them then you
really appreciate well yeah I can
totally read all like I'm at a Bangkok
shall come get the reason they're your
teachers your harlot are you good at
math is they they know something that
you would like to learn not be harmed me
do you know my good man whoa boy they
have certain habits or certain skills
that we would like to learn when you
talk Wayne Newton wanyan bina needed my
do not move upon so think about just any
one of those with very high gimme very
booty item so how are you why did you
choose them as a teacher a soccer player
soccer bank John all our high cumin what
do they have that you don't have how do
you gain market man come god
what the day that you want to learn
hopefully you get my take my new hop
home take about one thing ain't even a
mob new one good quality more some check
top
you
nothing ya aini the reason i see this
good quality the opinion type on your
table at night if we go back to the the
old popular pen teaching i don't know
why i buy how quaint oh no ding by
people because a dog and a human see a
pen as a different thing well become Joe
Pikul going in time we move nilaam over
cut now that shows that the 10 is coming
from the human's mind young people
banged into Fiat um J Congo and the same
object
Knowlton is being seen as a chew toy by
the dog Samuel I'm a bundle joining I'm
Michael John there for me the pen is not
coming from the pen then come then to
fake a book if the pen was coming from
the pendant both the dog and the human
would see it as a pen okay Boop now then
to fake a boutique a con job oh gosh I
can't I know a lot more people and the
reason the humans is a pen well your
noggin time more people is that they
have a seed in their mind nobody how
come opium don't dumb jihad and when
they look at the cylinder stick the pen
stick hung in Wow gateway and Jude are
where people when they look on those
parts then the seed opens in their mind
the onion one infant on tiptoe happy oh
no Tom Tom Jake aha
and an image made of life comes out of
the scene when handled out at the lunch
Aang Lena Kor have young and it settles
down on the pillow
well not from killing people on the
cylinder men hanjo da and that's why the
human sees a pen
well don idiotic ongoing in time okay
boo now how that
stayed got into the human's mind karmic
seed but now my young leave out I'm
Chicano yummy we're going to explore
that during the Wheel of Life
come father autumn show quato bunch a
new home but we all know because of the
first law of karma but I don't I do big
movie we looked all thinking it
watermelons make watermelons you how are
you how if I see an instrument of
communication like a pen in time uncle
y'all dip in new more people and that
comes out of a karmic seed in my mind
well you doggie daddy mommy John come
jiggle toy then I must have helped some
other people communicate in the past why
they toid Friday yep that vine whip a
q-tip - whoa cool
that also applies to the beautiful
quality I see in my teacher right now
up your nose why from check top their
union title Tyco Tony look night it's
coming from the seat in my mind not
enter my young TomTom j-pop oh and
because of the laws of karma we know
what I did to plant a seed is similar to
how I see my llama acting now toodle-oo
make you happy auntie - Tony Capp Tony
entice Villar Michael to handle Bahia
so the sweet quality that I see in my
llama
didn't item Vietnam market on a night
that's coming out of a state that I
planted by behaving like him or her in
my past lives do don't you dare to mock
up Yamamoto job market to show you my
Hawk away time will keep some to code
experience my teacher has a very patient
person no anger no don't go changing by
the hypotonia mom no looking young
communion then it must be that in one of
my past lives I was a person who didn't
have much English
no psyching young and keep chipped I
could totally come hi I'm gonna go and
sort of an exploration or detective
exploration when and gymnastic mogul
Tommy Tom Delta me or that quality that
I see in my teacher the patients for
example Hamiltonian tycoon with high eco
toy we only show Kingdom must have been
planted by me myself in a past life no
fine idea boy toy biting my tongue
Tomoki chota so let's go on an
exploration to our past life hey cuckoo
come up Chico - nah just in our
imagination
yeah jump so don't don't go too bad and
not many of us in this world have the
ability to see our personalized directly
welcome your gentle touch in the INA
coconut yantai captured on Tomoka chick
tip
but it's fun too gasps what did I do in
the past to see this you're not going to
wait at all to the lambda voiceover
cutting into a big knife
then use your imagination
Rachel Yugi don't go back right have fun
enjoy never done oh no we're trying to
find a powerful good seeds in our past
lies
nothing cool down the gym don't have
young dope and Marilyn keeps you and
make a movie in your mind
well he's your amiable team Tom Tom
chick man Oh in my past life
oh I don't get chewed I within him I was
threatened by some other countries
notably don't you you're about I
wouldn't not gonna tell but I was very
patient into the kingdom and I refused
to fight I refused to be angry
Jordan young daughter to join you after
further movie you're gonna have to
create a decide what country you are in
go chop simcha twang shall fight America
with the movie on our banner and what
body were you look at I now Bank economy
what race of people our culture of
people were you mankind and why now was
it last year or was it a hundred years
ago or a thousand years ago my hand on a
mope jump to thank me I loved you so
make this beautiful story fine and a
diagram a coach in there don't be shy
looking angle and make it sweet Nikki no
Jenna no no okay if you have a teacher
in this life or you can even imagine the
historical teacher in front of you a Jon
Kitna
what they don't over-tighten with so
there are cheap market where if you even
her
in this life the word Buddha or whether
word Muhammad or the word Jesus taiyaki
tonight though Mohammad Jew Jesus you're
a good person mañana
and you had some extraordinary
experiences in your past life
mojito packet my opinion we're gonna go
on a pretended exploration of our past
life I'll keep Jude cook a pan when I
jump touch it to put on him don't do I
keep to cook it man
just enjoy Chicano make it detailed
don't don't say I was patient like try
to imagine someone specific kind of
person looks like this tried to hit me I
was patient
okay I think you're not John and cheated
do not have toe the kingdom I come to
talk tied off more blowing you a coat I
know don't owe me tonight a coat and tie
toda King Yahoo chose
recently in my own case don't you put on
don't die if I just imagine my past life
I cannot see it directly no booty don't
get to go Toto companion tiny chip dip I
keep getting a woman from the Middle
East to come and I don't know maybe it
was thousand years ago big no-no but I
loved you and she's a physician she's a
doctor look away look away no more bad
shape they make a whole story about this
position so don't do that now that I'm a
coaching by goal they took nine so
you'll see the the photograph I put it
as the header for this class if I can
punch a type of an odor that long I'm
dude I chopped up like I found a picture
of I thought I found a picture online
who looked like her but iam not in pain
I can't go out on a timetable change of
doing much I'm Dominique away so let's
imagine fine and I don't know have fun I
move there don't get stuck don't stop if
we still have more time then slow down
and make a nice story will be my captain
your life you haven't gone you Taeyang
they H I'm live at our own mo coaching
hi this is a an exercise in the Wheel of
Life a bunch a new home this is an
exercise in dependent origination anime
mundo puto the shell is Dumbo Sutra says
now can-can dunno young and we're gonna
talk about it next class but you know a
kid named on a hop dictator thin
only if you see something why do you
doubt something made it happen
hey God knew ye daughter King Messiah so
let's make a movie where we'll take
about 10 minutes cool fool if you get
tired if you forget what you're doing
just come back but no but when McNew
market maintain hey why shall I keep
adding more and more detail hey time
Bonucci t-cannula
are you seeing your past life directly
my onions I get to go back to keep calm
I think in my case and most of us we are
not so we jump to my boat I were to bar
took the commune time I would just
imagining our past life kampachi then
don't keep joke or too bad yeah but
don't forget you know one time even a
movie you imagine in your mind some
cheap mobile feed my cat magnet
don'tjump Tom Jacob man those
imaginations in your mind are also
coming Francis jump time Jacob a pine
cone and Antonian have yeah you cannot
imagine patience of a woman a thousand
years ago yet man come taken dog - Hill
Qingyuan come on foo not a dime of
knowing Namjoo if you don't have seeds
for patience no go back home go ahead
Yamaguchi Kingdom in that sense higher
middle way school they who not you right
about now huh they would say this movie
we are pretending is as some reality
Honorable team Jim Paddington the Lanco
by forgotten okay let's go
enjoy she's a beautiful quality of your
teacher
hi John Moore from job to query Google
how you go get back make a beautiful
story now never coaching goofy hundred
years ago I'm Jude opening I'm Jude any
country you want what do ya know I might
have any more any person you want to be
dangling our markup anymore collected
the seeds to see this moment in my life
no they told me and have young lady in
tiny tiny night jumping some by yeah go
get man okay let's go your college um
type of now now
you
yes slowly come back yeah I thought oh
wait July
come back to the teacher sitting in
front of you well Jen I will multi tango
chick market by look at that same good
quality but now I appreciate it
differently come check top not anyway
yeah I dumped it not mo cut her in a way
it's part of me already cut my not a
llama phone call
I still have that quality also some some
of it
- Cubano from chapter or to come from
chapter
you
dedicate the good karma of this
meditation their seventh preliminary
anyone who need talk about a night move
mardow to buy
pray that all people could plant because
this like this one I can wing down to
come on over there but I only have yump
opieop I die
imagine a whole world of people like
that I don't don't talk about 'your they
all on you know young Rita
you can slowly open your eyes Michelle
don't get fine but I don't those mama
dad take a stretch thank you yeah now
that's dependent origination to it will
lead us into emptiness most young to die
well didn't come and that emptiness will
help us in the first of the 12 steps of
the wheel of dependent origination but
didn't come - yep - a book touting
Chumlee hi book opens engine doing see
you in session head hang up like a pan
off onto money
Thank You Stanley come on Stanley
you